A Guide to the Pocahontas Mines Collection, 1883-1997
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II. Unscanned rolls, 1883-1997, 360 Cubic Feet; 463 boxes
  - Prospecting (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map: No 3 Seam north of Guyandotte lease hold. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/01/02 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map: Sewell Seam on the Itmann Leasehold. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/01/08 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map of No. 3 Seam on the Guyandotte Leasehold. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/12/28 (Box 649)
    - Detail Drawing of Piers for Refuse Bin, Itmann mine, West Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1952/04/23 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map: Map Showing Outcrop of the Coal Seams on Itmann and Guyandotte Leaseholds, and area between the N.W. Boundary of Guyandotte Lease and Still Run Creek. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. a Division of Consolidation Coal Co., 1959/11/05 (Box 649)
    - Bottom Creek Leasehold contour map, undated (Box 649)
    - Map of Mines of the Eureka Coal And Coke Co.: No 9 Seam Workings. Situate at Eckman, McDowell Co., West Virginia, undated (Box 649)
    - Photocopy negative of unidentified room and pillar coal mine, undated (Box 649)
    - Section of unidentified topographic map (47 sheets), undated (Box 649)
    - Technical Drawing of hoisting drive and gear box, undated (Box 649)
    - Rolfe Grade, undated (Box 649)
  - Prospecting (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 649)
    - Prospecting on Eureka & Shawnee Seams. Eckman, West Virginia Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1944/11/11 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting on Eureka & Shawnee Seams. Eckman, West Virginia Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1944/12/29 (Box 649)
    - Crop Openings & Sections of No. 9 Seam. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1945/01/03 (Box 649)
    - Delta Prospecting Map -No. 11 Seam: Switchback, West Virginia, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1945/01/04 (Box 649)
    - Crop Openings & Sections and Analysis of No. 9 Seam. Eckman, West Virginia Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1945/01/12 (Box 649)
    - Crop Openings & Sections of No. 11 Seam. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1945/01/22 (Box 649)
    - Crop Openings & Sections of No. 11 Seam. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1945/01/23 (Box 649)
    - Crop Openings & Sections of No. 10 Seam. Eckman, West Virginia Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1945/01/25 (Box 649)
    - Crop Openings & Sections of No. 9 Seam. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1945/05/10 (Box 649)
    - Crop Openings & Sections of No. 11 Seam. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1945/05/10 (Box 649)
    - Crop Openings & Sections of No. 9 Seam. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1945/05/11 (Box 649)
    - Relation of seams on Pulaski Lease. Eckman, West Virginia Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1945/05/22 (Box 649)
    - No. 9 Seam Sections and Analysis on Pulaski Lease. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1945/06/22 (Box 649)
    - No. 9 Seam Sections and Analysis on Pulaski Lease. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1945/06/22 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Upper Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-1, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Upper Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-3, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Middle Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-4, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Middle Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-6, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Map of Guyandotte Leasehold (negative image) Pocahontas Land Corporation, 1946/05/15 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map: No. 3 Seam on the Guyandotte Leasehold. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1946/12/28 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map: No. 6 Seam on the Guyandotte Leasehold. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1946/12/28 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map: Fire Creek Seam on the Guyandotte Leasehold. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1946/12/28 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map - Beckley Seam: Tract of Coal Land bounded on the North by Lands of the Brule Smokeless Coal Co.; On the West by Still Run Creek; and on the Southeast by Guyandotte Lease of the Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1946/12/30 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map - No. 3 Seam: Tract of Coal Land bounded on the North by Lands of the Brule Smokeless Coal Co.; On the West by Still Run Creek; and on the Southeast by Guyandotte Lease of the Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/01/02 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map - No. 6 Seam: Tract of Coal Land bounded on the North by Lands of the Brule Smokeless Coal Co.; On the West by Still Run Creek; and on the Southeast by Guyandotte Lease of the Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/01/03 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map: No 3 Seam on the Itmann leasehold. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/01/07 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map: Sewell Seam on the Itmann Leasehold. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/01/08 (Box 649)
    - Map Showing Outcrop of the Coal on Itmann Leasehold. Guyandotte Leasehold and the Area between the N. W. Boundary of Guyandotte Lease and Still Run Creek. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/01/09 (Box 649)
    - Coal Sections from Mine Workings on the Itmann leasehold. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/07/03 (Box 649)
    - Role No. 3 and No 6 seam Channel Sections & proximate Analysis, 1948/11/16 (Box 649)
    - County Boundary Maps of Virginia - West Virginia 3781-1, undated (Box 649)
    - County Boundary Maps of Virginia - West Virginia 3781-2, undated (Box 649)
    - County Boundary Maps of Virginia - West Virginia 3781-2, undated (Box 649)
    - County Boundary Maps of Virginia - West Virginia 3781-5, undated (Box 649)
    - County Boundary Maps of Virginia - West Virginia 3781-5, undated (Box 649)
    - County Boundary Maps of Virginia - West Virginia 3781-6, undated (Box 649)
    - County Boundary Maps of Virginia - West Virginia 3781-7, undated (Box 649)
  - Miscellaneous Maps (Box 650)
    - Amonate mine, Dunford Portal. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1955/06/23 (Box 650)
    - Sow Mine: Plan. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1938/03/27 (Box 650)
    - Map showing yearly advance of Sagamore and Angle Mines, 1939/01/17 (Box 650)
    - Jenkin Jones Plan and Grades on No. 4 Seam Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., JJ-8-22, 1942/04/10 (Box 650)
    - Jenkin Jones Plan and Grades on No. 4 Seam Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., JJ-8-23, 1942/04/10 (Box 650)
    - Jenkin Jones Plan and Grades on No. 4 Seam Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., JJ-8-26, 1942/04/10 (Box 650)
    - Prospecting Sections on Bottom Creek Lease, Bottom Creek, West Virginia, 1943/07/27 (Box 650)
    - Prospecting drill hole locations on topographic map of Bottom Creek Lease, Bottom Creek, West Virginia, 1943/07/27 (Box 650)
    - Map Showing Graham Town Subdivision. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1953/03/18 (Box 650)
    - Map Showing Lots lying along North Side East Water Street Subdivision and South Side of Graham Town Subdivision No. 2. These Lots are Affected by the N&W Right of Way. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1953/06/09 (Box 650)
    - Map Showing Burnley Town Subdivision. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1953/10/22 (Box 650)
    - Map Showing Burnley Town Subdivision. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1953/10/22 (Box 650)
    - Map showing land lots near Pocahontas High School. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1954/07/29 (Box 650)
    - Map Showing Tract of Land Situated in the Right Fork of Crockett Cove, Near Bishop, Tazewell County, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1954/09/30 (Box 650)
    - Map showing school lot in the town of Boissevain, Tazewell County, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1955/04/06 (Box 650)
    - Untitled Section of topographic map photocopy, undated (Box 650)
    - Untitled Section of topographic map photocopy, undated (Box 650)
    - Untitled Section of topographic map photocopy, undated (Box 650)
    - Untitled Section of topographic map photocopy, undated (Box 650)
    - Untitled Section of topographic map photocopy, undated (Box 650)
    - Colored School Lot, East Sandmill Hollow. Pocahontas Virginia, undated (Box 650)
    - Map of Daniel Asbury private land plot, undated (Box 650)
    - Colored School Lot, East Sandmill Hollow. Pocahontas Virginia, undated (Box 650)
    - Colored School Lot, East Sandmill Hollow. Pocahontas Virginia, undated (Box 650)
    - Colored School Lot, East Sandmill Hollow. Pocahontas Virginia, undated (Box 650)
    - Untitled map of tract of land subdivided by Ollie S. Wynn and A.P. Sayers (Box 650)
    - Untitled map of land Near Virginia. State Highway to Bluefield and a Cemetery (Box 650)
  - Rolfe Mine/Tipple Technical Drawings (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Tipple: Foundation Drawing - Side View. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1926/05/10 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Mine: New 7' Aerovane Mine Fan. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1937/05/10 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] #31 Tipple Dry Pea. Rolfe Tipple Slack Bins: Detail of Base, 1940/02/02 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Tipple: Location Plan. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1940/02/05 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Tipple: Plan and elevation. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1940/02/06 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Tipple: Screen Detail. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1940/02/15 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Tipple: Bent Detail. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1940/02/19 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Tipple: Bent Detail. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1940/02/19 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Tipple: Shaft Detail. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1940/02/26 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Tipple: Shafting. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1940/02/26 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Tipple: 1/2" Scale Layout. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1940/02/28 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Tipple: Slack Screens. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1940/03/03 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Tipple: Pea Screens. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1940/03/08 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Preliminary Drawing & Estimate of Dump & Chute; for purpose of dumping No. 6. Seam Coal into trucks for loading through Tipple or separate loading ramp. Rolfe Mine, 1947/09/25 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Mine: Proposed Layout for Mine Openings, Tram Road, Track, and Dumping Facilities, on No. 6 Seam. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/11/20 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Tipple: Screen Layout. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1950/02/15 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Mine No. 6 Seam Profile from Bridge on Railroad Grade to 42+61 on -2% Grade from No. 6. Scale Pit. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1955/06/14 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Mine No. 6 Seam Profile from Bridge on Railroad Grade to 42+61 on -2% Grade from No. 6. Scale Pit, undated (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Rolfe Mine: Conversion of Pocahontas Mine Car Scales to Truck Scales - Plan & Section. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., undated (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] untitled sectional view of a tipple (2 sheets), undated (Box 650)
  - Crane Creek (Box 650)
    [Removed from map case drawer entitled "Sagamore".]
    - [Drawing] Crane Creek No. 11 Mine: Fan Layout and Location. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1957/04/08 (Box 650)
    - [Drawings] Crane Creek Preparation Plant Drawings. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Division of Consolidation Coal Company Co. (32 Sheets), 1959-1961 (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Crane Creek No. 11 Mine: Fan Detail. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., undated (Box 650)
    - Untitled Map of Crane Creek Mine workings and Surface Facilities. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., undated (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Untitled Profile of Crane Creek property; elevation and side view of Conveyor Feeder. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., undated (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Crane Creek-Sagamore Property Boundary. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Inc, undated (Box 650)
    - Untitled Map of Crane Creek Mine Surface Facilities. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., undated (Box 650)
    - [Drawing] Crane Creek: Proposed Truck Dump Point For Bone Coal. (Box 650)
  - Sagamore (Box 650)
    - Map of No. 11 Seam Outcrop on Sagamore, Cherokee, and Angle Leasehold and McDowell & Greenbrier Leases, 1949/03/20 (Box 650)
    - Map of No. 11 Seam Outcrop on Sagamore, Cherokee, and Angle Leasehold and McDowell & Greenbrier Leases, 1949/03/20 (Box 650)
    - Sagamore Tipple Area. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1952/10/10 (Box 650)
    - Sagamore Tipple Area. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1952/10/10 (Box 650)
    - [Drawings] Sagamore Colliery surface and plant facilities drawings. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (23 sheets), 1921-1961 (Box 650)
    - [Drawings] Sagamore No. 11 Seam Tramroad Bridge drawings. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (19 Sheets), 1944-1945 (Box 650)
  - Architectural & Construction Drawings (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 650)
    [Removed from map case drawer entitled "Supplies".]
    - [Drawings] Heyl & Patterson, Inc. Drawings of Itmann Prep Plant for Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (25 sheets), 1961 (Box 650)
    - [Drawings] Galis Electric & Machine Company drawings of Conveyors for Itmann Mine of Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (3 sheets), 1961/08/14 (Box 650)
    - [Drawings] Fireproof Products Co. Drawings of Truck Ramp at Itmann Mine for Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (9 Sheets), 1959/03-1959/05 (Box 650)
    - [Drawings] West Virginia Steel Corp. Drawings for Itmann Tipple (19 sheets), 1959/03-1959/07 (Box 650)
    - [Drawings] Itmann Mine Refinery Details for Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Drawn by William L. Clark, Jr. PE., Consulting Engineer (3 sheets), 1959/04/18 (Box 650)
    - Proposed Projection of Itmann Mine workings in No. 3 seam. Itmann leasehold, Itmann, West Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1959/05/25 (Box 650)
    - [Drawings] Mine Service Building - Mathews Mine: Consolidation Coal Company, Claiborne Tennessee. Design by David Leonard Associates (10 sheets), 1976/03/16 (Box 650)
    - [Drawings] Prelim #1 thru #4 of Itmann Railroad Rotary Dump (4 sheets), 1961/09/14 - 1961/09/15 (Box 650)
    - [Drawings] Shoemaker Mine - Wheeling Creek Portal Bath House Architectural Plans. 73-8, 110801, PP-1 (5 sheets), 1977/04/11 - 1977/04/26 (Box 650)
  - Kepler #2, undated (Box 651)
  - United States No. 1 Shaft. No. 4 Mine, undated (Box 651)
  - PLD-1633 Old Jim Fork Mine. 8-4 (Box 651)
  - PLD-1608. No. 14 mine. 2-4 (Box 651)
  - Peerless King Slope, undated (Box 652)
  - OSM #700728 Tidewater Mine no. 1 (Box 652)
  - OSM #700781 No. 1 mine Deerfield sheet no. 1 (Box 652)
  - OSM #700177. Modoc (Box 652)
  - OSM #700770, Nos. 1 and 4 mines, near Dan's Branch [West Virginia?] (Box 653)
  - OSM #700135, Berwind No. 1 Mine (Box 653)
  - OSM #700776, Lego Mine Map, No. 4 Seam, Meadows Mine, Janney No. 19 (Box 653)
  - OSM #700788. Lowen End War Creek Mains. (Box 653)
  - OSM #700805 Arista No. 4 (Box 654)
  - Booth Bowen. (Box 655)
  - PLD-1483.01 thru 1483.03. Lick Branch (Box 656)
  - PLD-1482 Indian Ridge. (Box 657)
  - PLD-1481.01 thru 1481.04. Gillman C & C Co. (Box 657)
  - PLD-1484. Elkhorn and Shamokin (Box 657)
  - OSM #700756, Crozer Land Association, Charmco Mine, Fire Creek Seam (Box 657)
  - OSM #700723, No. 9 Seam, Crane Creek (Box 657)
  - OSM #700792, Berwin, 61, All-Mine, undated (Box 658)
  - Barkers Creek Coal Co., Beckley Seam, Mine Map (Box 658)
  - PLD- 1501 thru PLD-1501.02, Greenbrier. (Box 658)
  - Hemphill Colliery, Welch, West Virginia PLD-1498.01 thru PLD-1498.03 (Box 658)
  - Algoma, Piney Mine, PLD-1480.01 thru PLD-1480.04 (Box 658)
  - Buckeye. PLD-1497 (Box 659)
  - Mine Map No. 1 of Loup Creek Colliery Company, Page Fayette County W. Virginia, Eagle Vein, undated (Box 660)
  - Map of Mines of the Thomas Coal Co., McComas West Virginia, PLD-1502.01 thru PLD-1502.05, undated (Box 660)
  - Barkers creek Coal Co., No. 6 Seam. (Box 660)
  - OSM #7007848, Rolfe Showing Pinnacle Creek, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (Box 660)
  - OSM #700778, Pickshin Mine, Sheet No. 2 (Box 660)
  - OSM #700745, Berwin, No. 10 Mine, 65, No. 3 Seam. (Box 661)
  - OSM #700739, Killarney - Sheet No. 2, 7 -North. (Box 661)
  - OSM #700809, Arista, Ford and Chrysler panels. (Box 661)
  - OSM #700835, No. 8, Some Augering (Box 661)
  - OSM #700804, Page No. 11 seam. 41 (Box 661)
  - OSM #700812, Bailey Wood (Box 661)
  - Aerial Photographs (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] Aerial Composite Photograph of South Eastern West Virginia. Sheets 13 thru 41. U.S. Department of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service, 1946/06/03 (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] Aerial Composite Photograph of Tazewell County, Virginia, U.S. Department of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service (4 sheets), 1953/08/28 (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] Aerial Composite Photograph of Bland County, Virginia. Sheets 2 of 4. U.S. Department of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service, 1954/12/28 (Box 662)
    - Map of Mary Brown Property, 1956/09/25 (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] Aerial Composite Photograph of Raleigh County, West Virginia. Sheets 1 thru 4. U.S. Department of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service, 1958/10/23 (Box 662)
  - Aerial Photographs (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] Index photograph of Crozer Coal and Land Company, Lynco, West Virginia (2 sheets), 1955/12 (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] 129- 2A-18 (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] 1294, 1335 thru 1336,1378 thru 1379, 1405 thru 1440 (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] BCH- 2K- 35 thru BCH-2K-66 (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] BCH-1K- 186 thru BCH-1K-196 (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] BCH-1K- 125 thru BCH-1K-133 (Box 662)
  - Aerial Photographs (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] DTO-8L-114, DTO-8L-116, DTO-8L-120, DTO-8L-122, 1953/05/29 (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] DLC-12P-35, DLC-12P-37, 1955/09/03 (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] DZL-5R-105, Taken 1967/05/06, location unknown., 1967/05/06 (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] 1300, 1384, 1432, 1709 (Box 662)
    - [Aerial Photographs] Composite photographs of Bluefield and Wytheville areas. numbered: 14, 21, 22. (Box 662)
  - OSM #700734, Map showing mine workings, tipple, railroads, coke ovens, & houses belonging to Louisville Coal & Coke Co. Goodwill, West Virginia, 1904/08/13 (Box 663)
  - OSM #700796, Tidewater Coal & Co. No. 1 Mine, 1919/10 (Box 663)
  - OSM #700823, Lillybrook (Box 663)
  - OSM #700817, Delta Lease (Turkey Gap), No. 11 seam (Box 663)
  - OSM #700780, Crane Creek, No. 11 Seam. Greenbrier lease. (Box 663)
  - OSM #700782, Unidentified Mine, No. 4 Mains on Barkers Creek. (Box 663)
  - OSM #7007865, Mine Map of Lynchburg Coal And Coke Co., Kyle, McDowell Counties, West Virginia., 1894/11/17 (Box 664)
  - Deerfield No. 1 Mine, Sheet No. 2 (Box 664)
    Map has draftsman's doodle art of a Native woman in middle of a blank space.
  - OSM #7007838, Daniel Mains, Cove 5 Left panel (Box 664)
  - OSM #700795, Sagamore, Map no. 2. No. 6 gas seam (Box 664)
  - OSM #700798, Itmann No. 3 mine. 3-B shaft (Box 664)
  - OSM #700750, J. M. Smith Tract adjoining P.L.C. Prop., Smith Seam, Stripping (Box 664)
  - OSM #700718, unidentified mine, ca. 1960s (Box 665)
  - OSM #700348, Gordie and C.V. #2 overlay, Gordie Coal Co., Tazewell, Virginia (Box 665)
  - OSM #700714, No. 3 Mines, Pineville Mains (Box 665)
  - OSM #700347, Arista No. 4, Top Half of Arista Mains, Noseman Portal adjoining Arista Mine (Box 665)
  - OSM #700769, Lick Branch-Shamokin 200. Angle Delta?? (Box 666)
  - OSM #700815, 103 Caswell Cr. Hemlock., Caswell Creek Lease, Mercer Co., West Virginia, [Carswell Creek Mine] (Box 666)
  - OSM #700779, Part of East Mine (Box 666)
  - OSM #700830, unidentified map (Box 666)
  - OSM #700777, No. 1 Mine, Lillybrook No. 4 Seam, No. 3 Mine at Tipple, Town of Fireco, Leckie Firecreek Coal Co. (Box 666)
  - OSM #700732, Wenonah 1-2-3 Mines, #200 (Box 666)
  - OSM #700818, Map of Mines, Covel Smokeless Coal Co., Covel, West Virginia (Box 667)
  - OSM #700848, Turkey Gap Lower End 2nd Rt, [Northwest Slope?] 3 Seam (Box 667)
  - OSM #700844, Craine Creek #6, Drift & 1st Right, New 2nd left Parallel & Miner Sections, No. 4 (Box 667)
  - OSM #700851, Piedmont, Sheet 2. (Box 667)
  - OSM #700816, No. 6, 7, 8 (Box 667)
  - OSM #700850, Turkey Gap, Rich Creek Mains, 2nd Right Section (Box 667)
  - OSM #700828, 51, Nassau [Coal Company?] No. 3 Seam (Box 668)
  - OSM #700787, 85, Cherokee No. 1 Mine, Upper Horsepen Seam, Bundy Virginia. (Box 669)
  - OSM #700765, Thomas Mains #2, Pinnacle Strip (Box 669)
  - OSM #700771, Itmann No. 3 Mine, 10 and 11 panel (Box 669)
  - OSM #700774, Pemberton Coal & Coke Company, Phillips Mine (Box 669)
  - OSM #700229, G. O., 124, Shamokin and Lick Branch, No. 3 Seam, ca. 1930s-1940s (Box 670)
  - OSM #700793, unnamed property (Box 670)
  - OSM #700773, 3 maps - B.S. #1 Drift, Ragland Slope, Wat Wise Slope, Baileywood to 17 left (Box 670)
  - OSM #700134, Berwind No. 1 Mine, Main Right. (Box 671)
  - OSM #700801, Itmann No. 3. (Box 671)
  - OSM #700826, Sagamore No. 1, No. 3 seam, 118 (Box 671)
  - OSM #700794, unidentified longwall mine (Box 672)
  - OSM #700852, New Mine [?], Section - 1 (Box 672)
  - OSM #700151, Itmann No. 2 Mine. (Box 672)
  - OSM #700807, 11-C, Crane Creek No. 2 (Box 672)
  - OSM #700741, Sagamore #11, Greenbrier Lease, #3 Crane Creek, No. 11-A (Box 673)
  - OSM #700475 [Big Stick?] Sec-1 (Box 673)
  - OSM #700716, Crane Creek, #11 Seam, No. 1 (Box 673)
  - OSM #700722, Buckeye. (Box 673)
  - [Aerial Photographs] 658-2-71 thru 658-1- 90, 1965/12/06 (Box 674)
  - [Aerial Photographs] 658-4-29 thru 658-3- 64, 1965/12/07 (Box 675)
  - [Aerial Photographs] 863-89, 863-212, location unknown. (Box 676)
  - [Aerial Photographs] 293A-37 thru 293A-124 (Box 676)
  - U.S. Coal & Coke Company. No. 2, 5, 6, 6 East, 7, 8, and 11 Mines. 4-5, undated (Box 677)
  - OSM #700790, Piedmont #2. No. 3 Seam (Box 677)
  - Map 13, Unidentified Mine of Central Pocahontas Coal Co. (Box 677)
  - Ashland Mine on North Fork of Elkhorn River (Box 678)
  - Angle, Carswell Creek Mine (Box 679)
  - Keystone Mine + Algoma C&C Co. Air Courses (Box 680)
  - U.S. Coal & Coke Company. No. 6, 7, and 8 Mines. 4-6, undated (Box 681)
  - U. S. Coal & Coke Co., No 9 East and No. 9 West mines, No. 4 seam. 4-7 (Box 681)
  - PLD-1606, Ridge Land Co., No. 3 Seam, No. 12 Mine, Mill Creek, North and Little Forks of Tug River, ca. 1940s-1960s (Box 682)
  - OSM #700716, Map of Modoc, Beginning of Arista Mains (Cuts off at border line), Turkey Gap, Inactive (Box 682)
  - OSM #700114, Bishop Stripping, Horsepen Seams (Box 682)
  - 4 maps, including Cassidy Branch No. 3 BF Eagle, Chandler Coal Co., and others (Box 683)
  - OSM #700766, Itmann #1 & #4 mines, U.S. Steel Boundary and Guyan Mains, No. 3 seam (Box 683)
  - OSM #700784, Mine Map of The Devils Fork Coal Co. (Lessee of the Pocahontas Coal and Coke Co.) on the waters of the Guyandotte River, Wyoming County, West Virginia, 1918/06/21 (Box 684)
  - OSM #700747, Page Coal & Coke Co. #9 seam (Box 684)
  - 39. OSM #700786, Elk Ridge, Eureka No. 9 Seam outcrop (Box 684)
  - 52. OSM #700749, Nassau, No. 3 seam (Box 684)
  - OSM #700737, Jenkin Jones No. 9, V Entry (Box 684)
  - OSM #700772, Turkey Gap (Box 684)
  - 71. OSM #700843, Excelsior Williams Pocahontas Berwind (Box 685)
  - OSM #700841, Goodwill No.2 Mine and Sagamore Mine, No. 6 seam (Box 685)
  - 53. OSM #700799, Nassau, No. 4 Seam (Box 685)
  - OSM #700808, Itmann #1 Mine, A - Entry Side (Box 685)
  - Itmann Technical Drawings (Box 686)
    - Machinist drawings for steel parts and pieces for Itmann Prep Plant by Fairmont Machinery Co., 1958 (Box 686)
    - Dry Coal Cross Conveyor for Itmann Prep Plant drawing by Robertson Co., 1958/10/09 (Box 686)
    - General Arrangement and Flow sheets for Itmann Prep Plant. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Div. of Consolidation Coal Co., 1959/09/30 (Box 686)
    - Construction plans for Itmann Preparation Plant drawn by Heyl & Patterson Inc. Contracting Engineers, 1968/09/30 (Box 686)
    - Fine Coal Cleaning Addition drawings by West Virginia Steel Corp., 1957/10/04 - 1957/10/09 (Box 686)
    - Conveyor plans and layout drawings by Alder F. Castanoli, Consulting Mining Engineer, undated (Box 686)
  - Peerless Coal & Coke Company (Box 686)